[
     {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [64, 64, 65, 61, 64, 66, 64, 63, 67, 68, 62]?",
      "correctAnswer": "64",
      "options": [
        "63",
        "64",
        "65",
        "66"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [69, 67, 67, 67, 67, 64, 66, 68, 63, 67, 65, 62]?",
      "correctAnswer": "67",
      "options": [
        "66",
        "67",
        "68",
        "69"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [69, 66, 68, 68, 70, 67, 65, 63, 64, 68]?",
      "correctAnswer": "68",
      "options": [
        "67",
        "68",
        "69",
        "70"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [71, 66, 69, 65, 69, 67, 69, 64, 68, 70, 69]?",
      "correctAnswer": "69",
      "options": [
        "68",
        "69",
        "70",
        "71"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [68, 71, 69, 65, 72, 70, 70, 66, 67, 70, 70, 70]?",
      "correctAnswer": "70",
      "options": [
        "69",
        "70",
        "71",
        "72"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [70, 69, 67, 72, 68, 73, 68, 66, 68, 71]?",
      "correctAnswer": "68",
      "options": [
        "67",
        "68",
        "69",
        "70"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [73, 70, 67, 74, 71, 69, 69, 72, 69, 69, 68]?",
      "correctAnswer": "69",
      "options": [
        "68",
        "69",
        "70",
        "71"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [75, 69, 69, 74, 68, 71, 69, 70, 73, 69, 69, 72]?",
      "correctAnswer": "69",
      "options": [
        "68",
        "69",
        "70",
        "71"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [70, 75, 73, 76, 74, 76, 72, 71, 76, 69]?",
      "correctAnswer": "76",
      "options": [
        "75",
        "76",
        "77",
        "78"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [70, 75, 77, 75, 72, 75, 76, 75, 74, 73, 71]?",
      "correctAnswer": "75",
      "options": [
        "74",
        "75",
        "76",
        "77"
      ]
    }
]